The untold story behind "We Are the World."
The Greatest Night in Pop is a documentary, music film directed by Bao Nguyen.
On a January night in 1985, music's biggest stars gathered to record "We Are the
World." This documentary goes behind the scenes of the historic event.
Self, played by Lionel Richie.
Self, played by Bruce Springsteen.
Self, played by Dionne Warwick.
Self, played by Kenny Loggins.
Self, played by Huey Lewis.
Self, played by Cyndi Lauper.
The Greatest Night in Pop is a 2024 documentary film directed by Bao Nguyen.
The film is about the creation of the renowned pop song "We
Are the World" and its recording in 1985.
The film features interviews with various people involved in the song, including Lionel Richie, Michael
Jackson, Stevie Wonder, Bruce Springsteen, Huey Lewis, Dionne Warwick, and Cyndi Lauper.
The film explores themes of pop culture, behind the scenes,
music recording, nostalgic, songwriting.
The tone is uplifting.